Guide to the Garrett Orr Papers, circa 1873-1994, bulk 1890s-1914, 1935-1965
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Product Files Series, 1915-1994 and undated
  - Print Advertisements Subseries, 1915-1994 and undated
    - Small Formats, 1915-1994 and undated
      - Advertising agencies (also in Large-Formats category)
        - Clippings and miscellaneous, undated (Box 8)
        - Foster and Kleiser (Box 8)
        - Miscellaneous postings (Box 8)
      - Automobiles and motorcycles
        - American Motors (Box 8)
        - Buick, 1930-1971 (Box 8)
        - Cadillac (also in Large-Formats category), 1930-1973 (Box 8)
        - Chevrolet (also in Large-Formats category), 1915-1980 (Box 8)
        - Chrysler (also in Large-Formats category), 1937-1967 (Box 8)
        - De Soto (also in Large-Formats category), 1940-1955 (Box 8)
        - Dodge (also in Large-Formats category), 1930-1970 (Box 8)
        - Ford (also in Large-Formats category), 1920-1970 (Box 8)
        - Foreign cars (also in Large-Formats category), 1960-1979 (Box 8)
        - General Motors (Box 8)
        - Hupmobile (Box 8)
        - International Truck and Engine Corporation (also in Large-Formats category) (Box 8)
        - Jeep, 1945-1972 (Box 8)
        - Mercury (Box 8)
        - Motorcycles, all makes (Box 8)
        - Oldsmobile (Box 8)
        - Packard (Box 8)
        - Plymouth (Box 8)
        - Pontiac, 1952-1966 (Box 8)
        - Rambler (Box 8)
        - [REO: see Large-Format category] (Box 8)
        - Studebaker, 1949-1964 (Box 8)
        - [Suzuki: see Large-Format category] (Box 8)
        - VIM, 1917 (Box 8)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 8)
      - Automotive parts and supplies
        - Gas/Oil
          - Amoco (also in Large-Formats category) (Box 8)
          - Atlantic (Box 8)
          - BP ( British Petroleum) (Box 8)
          - Citgo (Box 8)
          - Conoco (Box 8)
          - Esso/Enco/Exxon/Humble (Box 8)
          - Ethyl (Box 8)
          - [Gulf: see Large-Format category] (Box 8)
          - Havoline (Box 8)
          - Marathon (Box 8)
          - Mobilgas (also in Large-Formats category), 1964 and undated (Box 8)
          - Phillips 66, 1960 and undated (Box 8)
          - Pure/Union 76 (also in Large-Formats category) (Box 8)
          - Richfield, 1960 and undated (Box 8)
          - Shell, 1959-1960 and undated (Box 8)
          - Sinclair (Box 8)
          - Standard (Box 8)
          - Sunoco (Box 8)
          - Texaco/Tenneco (Box 8)
          - Miscellaneous (Box 8)
        - Parts and Accessories (also in Large-Formats category)
          - Batteries (Box 8)
          - Tires (also in Large-Formats category) (Box 8)
          - Miscellaneous (Box 8)
      - Banks
        - Arizona Bank (Box 8)
        - Bank of America (Box 8)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 8)
        - Stock posters for banking advertising (Box 8)
      - Beverages
        - Alcoholic beverages
          - Beer (Box 8)
          - Miscellaneous (Box 8)
        - Coffee and tea (also in Large-Formats category) (Box 8)
        - Juice (Box 8)
        - Soft drinks (also in Large-Formats category)
          - Coca-Cola, 1957-1965, (Folder 1 of 2) (Box 8)
          - Coca-Cola, 1957-1965 (continued), (Folder 2 of 2) (Box 9)
          - Pepsi Cola (Box 9)
          - Royal Crown (RC) Cola (Box 9)
          - Miscellaneous (Box 9)
      - Business
        - Building materials (Box 9)
        - Insurance (also in Large-Formats category) (Box 9)
        - Paint (Box 9)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 9)
      - Cameras and film (Box 9)
      - Drugs and toiletries
        - Anacin (Box 9)
        - Burma Shave, 1941-1994 (Box 9)
        - Drugs, over-the-counter (OTC) (Box 9)
        - Toiletries (Box 9)
      - Farm and garden (also in Large-Formats category) (Box 9)
      - Film posters (Box 9)
      - Food (also in Large-Formats category)
        - Candy (Box 9)
        - Cereal and breakfast products (Box 9)
        - Dairy products (Box 9)
        - Flour products (Box 9)
        - Frozen food (Box 9)
        - Fruits (Box 9)
        - Meats (Box 9)
        - Pet food (Box 9)
        - Prepared foods (Box 9)
        - Spices
          - Salt (Box 9)
          - Sugar (Box 9)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 9)
      - Household
        - Appliances (also in Large-Formats category)
          - Air conditioner (Box 9)
          - Dishwasher (Box 9)
          - Ovens (Box 9)
          - Stereo (Box 9)
          - Telephone (Box 9)
          - Television (Box 9)
          - Washer/Dryer (Box 9)
          - Miscellaneous (Box 9)
        - Cleaning supplies (Box 9)
        - Furnishings (Box 9)
        - Home heating/Air conditioning/Hot water (Box 9)
        - Paper products (Box 9)
        - Utilities (Box 9)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 9)
      - International advertisements (Box 9)
      - Personal products (also in Large-Formats category) (Box 9)
      - Political campaigns (Box 9)
      - Publications and media (also in Large-Formats category) (Box 9)
      - Public service (Box 9)
      - Radio/Television (Box 9)
      - Real estate (Box 9)
      - Restaurants (Box 10)
        - Kentucky Fried Chicken (Box 10)
        - McDonald's (Box 10)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 10)
      - Retail (also in Large-Formats category)
        - Clothing (also in Large-Formats category) (Box 10)
        - Department stores (Box 10)
        - Drug stores (Box 10)
        - Florists (Box 10)
        - Footwear (Box 10)
        - Grocery stores (also in Large-Formats category) (Box 10)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 10)
      - Sports (also in Large-Formats category)
        - Boating (Box 10)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 10)
      - Tobacco products (also in Large-Formats category) (Box 10)
      - Travel and transportation
        - Airlines (Box 10)
        - Vacation sites (Box 10)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 10)
    - Large Formats, 1959 and undated
      - Advertising-generic images (Box 11)
        - Children featured in advertisements (Box 11)
        - Christmas-related advertisements (Box 11)
      - Advertising agencies (Box 11)
      - Automobiles
        - Cadillac (Box 11)
        - Chevrolet (Box 11)
        - Chrysler (Box 11)
        - De Soto (Box 11)
        - Dodge (Box 11)
        - Ford (Box 11)
        - Foreign cars (Box 11)
        - International Scout (Box 11)
        - REO (Box 11)
        - Suzuki (Box 11)
      - Automotive
        - Gas/Oil
          - Amoco (Box 11)
          - Gulf (Box 11)
          - Mobilgas (Box 11)
          - Pure (Box 11)
        - Parts
          - Harrison Air Conditioning (Box 11)
          - Dunlop tires (Box 11)
      - Beverages
        - Coffee/Tea
          - Maxwell House (Box 11)
          - Sanka (Box 11)
        - Soft drinks
          - Cliquot Club (Box 11)
      - Business--Insurance (Box 11)
      - Farm and garden 1959 (Box 11)
      - Food (Box 11)
      - Household appliances (Box 11)
      - Personal products (Box 11)
      - Publications and media (Box 11)
      - Retail
        - Clothing (Box 11)
        - Grocery stores (Box 11)
      - Sports (Box 11)
      - Tobacco products (Box 11)
  - Photographs subseries, 1940s-1970s and undated
    - Advertising industry self-promotion (Box 12)
      - Billboards (Box 12)
      - Children featured in advertisements (Box 12)
      - Foster & Kleiser-produced images
        - Media Group, 1960s (Box 12)
        - Street scenes (Box 12)
        - Miscellaneous, (2 folders) (Box 12)
      - Shelving/Displays (OAAA) (Box 12)
    - Automobiles
      - American Motors, Javelin ITC (Box 12)
      - Buick (Box 12)
      - Cadillac, La Salle (Box 12)
      - Chevrolet (includes trucks), 1940s-1960 and undated, (4 folders) (Box 12)
      - Chrysler (Box 12)
      - Datsun (Box 12)
      - De Soto (Box 12)
      - Dodge (includes trucks), (2 folders) (Box 12)
      - Ford (includes trucks), (5 folders) (Box 13)
      - Foreign cars (Box 13)
      - General Motors (Box 13)
      - Hudson (Box 13)
      - Hupmobile (Box 13)
      - International Truck and Engine Corporation (includes trucks and tractors) (Box 13)
      - Jeep (Box 13)
      - Kaiser-Frazer (Box 13)
      - Lincoln (Box 13)
      - Mercury (Box 13)
      - Motorcycles (Box 13)
      - Nash (Box 13)
      - Oldsmobile (Box 13)
      - Plymouth (Box 13)
      - Pontiac (Box 13)
      - Rambler (Box 13)
      - REO (Box 13)
      - Studebaker-Packard (Box 13)
      - Miscellaneous automobiles (Box 14)
    - Automotive parts and supplies
      - Gas/Oil
        - Amoco (Box 14)
        - Atlantic (Box 14)
        - Calso (Box 14)
        - Chevron (Standard Oil of California) (Box 14)
        - Cities Service Co. (Box 14)
        - Conoco (Box 14)
        - Crown (Box 14)
        - El Paso (Box 14)
        - Esso, (3 folders) (Box 14)
        - Ethyl Gas Corporation (Box 14)
        - Fina (Box 14)
        - Gulf (Box 14)
        - Hancock (Box 14)
        - Marathon (Box 15)
        - Mobil (Box 15)
        - Norwalk (Box 15)
        - Phillips 66 (Box 15)
        - Pure motor oil (Box 15)
        - Richfield (Box 15)
        - Shell (Box 15)
        - Signal (Box 15)
        - Sinclair (Box 15)
        - Sohio (Box 15)
        - Standard, (2 folders) (Box 15)
        - Sunoco (Box 15)
        - Texaco (Box 15)
        - Wilshire (Box 15)
        - Miscellaneous gasoline (Box 15)
      - Parts and accessories
        - AC (Auto Care) spark plugs and other parts (Box 15)
        - Atlas batteries (Box 15)
        - Auto-Lite batteries (Box 15)
        - Cristy Drygas (Box 15)
        - Delco batteries (Box 15)
        - Dowgard (Box 15)
        - FRAM auto filters (Box 16)
        - Harrison automotive air conditioning (Box 16)
        - Heet gas line anti-freeze (Box 16)
        - Mark IV air conditioning (Box 16)
        - Monroe Load Levers (Box 16)
        - Motorola car radios (Box 16)
        - Prestone/Union Carbide coolant (Box 16)
        - Pyro/Super antifreeze (Box 16)
        - WIX (WIX Corporation of Gastonia, N.C.) (Box 16)
        - Zerex/DuPont, Telar antifreeze (Box 16)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 16)
      - Tires
        - Atlas (Box 16)
        - Chemstrand Nylon (Box 16)
        - Dunlop (Box 16)
        - Federal (Box 16)
        - Fisk (Box 16)
        - General (Box 16)
        - Goodrich (Box 16)
        - Goodyear (Box 16)
        - Kelly Springfield (Box 16)
        - Pure (Box 16)
        - U.S. Royal (Box 16)
        - Miscellaneous, 1950s-1970s (Box 16)
    - Banks
      - Bank of America (Box 16)
      - Chase Manhattan Bank (Box 16)
      - First National Bank (Ariz.) (Box 16)
      - National City Bank (Cleveland?) (Box 16)
      - Wells Fargo (Box 16)
      - Miscellaneous Banks, (2 folders) (Box 16)
      - Stock Posters (Box 16)
    - Beverages
      - Alcoholic
        - Beer
          - Acme (Box 16)
          - Ballantine's (Box 16)
          - Blatz (Box 16)
          - Blitz Weinhard (Box 16)
          - Budweiser (Box 16)
          - Hamm's (Box 16)
          - Kirin (Box 16)
          - Michelob (Box 16)
          - Miller's (Box 17)
          - Narraganset (includes ale) (Box 17)
          - Olympia (Box 17)
          - Pabst (Box 17)
          - Rainier (Box 17)
          - Schaefer (Box 17)
          - Schlitz (Box 17)
          - Miscellaneous (Box 17)
        - Wine
          - Ambassador (Box 17)
          - Brangno (Box 17)
          - Guild (Box 17)
          - Mogen David (Box 17)
          - Petri (Box 17)
          - Taylor champagne (Box 17)
          - Miscellaneous (Box 17)
        - Miscellaneous spirits
          - Ancient Age Kentucky bourbon (Box 17)
          - Antique bourbon whiskey (Box 17)
          - Appleton rum (Box 17)
          - Aristocrat brandy (Box 17)
          - Ballantine's whiskey (Box 17)
          - Canadian Club whiskey (Box 17)
          - Christian Bros. brandy (Box 17)
          - Coronet (Box 17)
          - Crawford's Scotch whiskey (Box 17)
          - Cutty Sark (Box 17)
          - Dewar's whiskey (Box 17)
          - Gilbey's gin (Box 17)
          - Hennessy cognac (Box 17)
          - Hine cognac (Box 17)
          - J.B. Scotch (Box 17)
          - Jack Daniel's whiskey (Box 17)
          - Jim Beam whiskey (Box 17)
          - Johnny Walker Scotch whiskey (Box 17)
          - Lord Calvert Canadian whiskey (Box 17)
          - Old Bushmill's Irish whiskey (Box 17)
          - Old Charter bourbon (Box 17)
          - Old Kentucky Tavern bourbon (Box 17)
          - Old Taylor (Box 17)
          - Ronrico rum (Box 17)
          - Royal Canadian whiskey (Box 17)
          - Schenley whiskey (Box 17)
          - Seagram's whiskey (Box 17)
          - Stolichnaya vodka (Box 17)
          - Tanqueray rum (Box 17)
          - Miscellaneous (Box 17)
      - Coffee and tea
        - Folger's (Box 17)
        - Lipton (Box 17)
        - Maxwell House (Box 18)
        - Salada (Box 18)
        - Sanka (Box 18)
        - Savarin (Box 18)
        - Yuban (Box 18)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 18)
      - Fruit juices
        - Juice mixes (Box 18)
        - Musselman's apple juice and sauce (Box 18)
        - V-8 vegetable juices (Box 18)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 18)
      - Soft drinks
        - Bireley's (Box 18)
        - Canada Dry and Spur (Box 18)
        - Clicquot Club ginger ale (Box 18)
        - Coca-Cola, (2 folders) (Box 18)
        - Dr. Pepper (Box 18)
        - Frostie root beer (Box 18)
        - Grapette (Box 18)
        - Kool-Aid (Box 18)
        - Nesbit's (Box 18)
        - Orange Crush (Box 18)
        - Pepsi (Box 18)
        - Royal Crown Cola (RC) (Box 18)
        - Seven-Up, (Folder 1 of 2) (Box 18)
        - Seven-Up (continued), (Folder 2 of 2) (Box 19)
        - Shasta (Box 19)
        - Squirt (Box 19)
        - Tang drink mix (Box 19)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 19)
    - Business and Industry
      - Building materials (Box 19)
      - Cans (Box 19)
      - Cemeteries/Funeral homes (Box 19)
      - Insurance (Box 19)
      - MasterCard (Box 19)
      - Paints
        - Foster & Kleiser-produced advertisements, 1960s-1970s (Box 19)
        - Sherwin Williams (Box 19)
      - Reynolds Aluminum (Box 19)
      - Schools (Box 19)
      - Pens and Stationary, 1950s (Box 19)
      - Steel, 1960s (Box 19)
      - Yellow Pages (Box 19)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 19)
    - Cameras and photographs
      - Kodak film (Box 19)
      - Polaroid Land Camera (Box 19)
      - Portrait, 1950s-1960s (Box 19)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 19)
    - Christmas (Box 19)
    - Drugs and toiletries
      - Anacin (Box 19)
      - Drugs, over-the-counter (OTC), (2 folders) (Box 19)
      - Hair care (Box 19)
      - Palmolive soap (Box 19)
      - Procter and Gamble (Box 19)
      - Shaving supplies (Box 19)
      - Skin care (Box 19)
      - Toiletries (Box 20)
      - Toothpaste
        - Colgate (Box 20)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 20)
    - Farm and garden
      - Agricultural (Box 20)
      - Fertilizers and insecticides (Box 20)
      - Zolone insect control (Box 20)
    - Film and television (Box 20)
    - Food
      - Bread and baked goods
        - Baked goods, breads and rolls, (2 folders) (Box 20)
        - Blue Seal (Box 20)
        - Bond (Box 20)
        - Holsum (Box 20)
        - Langendorf (Box 20)
        - Merita (Box 20)
        - Millbrook Co. (Nabisco) (Box 20)
        - Sunbeam, (2 folders) (Box 20)
        - Taystee, (Folder 1 of 2) (Box 20)
        - Taystee (continued), (Folder 2 of 2) (Box 21)
        - Tip-Top (Box 21)
        - Weber (Butternut, Mrs. Karl's, and Roman Meal) (Box 21)
        - Wonder (Box 21)
      - Cakes, cookies, snack foods
        - Archway (Box 21)
        - Drake's (Box 21)
        - Grennan, includes a cookbook (Box 21)
        - Hostess cupcakes (Box 21)
        - Lance cookies (Box 21)
        - Nabisco crackers (Box 21)
        - Ry-Krisp crackers (Box 21)
        - Sunshine (Box 21)
        - Tastykake and Tasty-Pie (Box 21)
        - Ward Bakery (Box 21)
        - Miscellaneous cakes, cookies, etc. (Box 21)
        - Miscellaneous crackers (Box 21)
      - Candy
        - Lifesavers (Box 21)
        - Mars (Box 21)
        - Tootsie Rolls (Box 21)
        - Wrigley's (Box 21)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 21)
      - Cereal
        - Kellogg's (Box 21)
        - Natural Oats oatmeal (Box 21)
        - Post (Box 21)
        - Quaker Oats, includes Aunt Jemima (Box 21)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 21)
      - Chips (Box 22)
        - Fritos (Box 22)
        - Gordon's Riplets (Box 22)
        - Morton's (includes Chip-O's) (Box 22)
        - New Era (Box 22)
        - Wise (Box 22)
        - Miscellaneous, (2 folders) (Box 22)
      - Dairy
        - Allsweet margarine (Box 22)
        - Borden's (Box 22)
        - Carnation (Box 22)
        - Coleman ice cream (Box 22)
        - Dairygold (Box 22)
        - Hygeia (Box 22)
        - Imperial margarine (Box 22)
        - Knudsen dairy (Box 22)
        - Milk and general (Wisconsin Dairy Association) (Box 22)
        - Nucoa margarine (Box 22)
        - Tri-Nut margarine (Box 22)
        - Miscellaneous butter, oleomargarine, peanut butter and other table spreads, (2 folders) (Box 22)
      - Flour and starch products (Box 22)
      - Frozen foods
        - Bird's Eye (Box 22)
        - Pictsweet, (2 folders) (Box 22)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 22)
      - Fruits
        - Dole (Box 22)
        - Ocean Spray cranberries (Box 22)
        - Sunkist (Box 22)
        - Sunmaid (Box 22)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 22)
      - Meats
        - Armour (Box 22)
        - Bacon, 1950s-1970s (Box 22)
        - Beef, 1950s-1960s (Box 22)
        - Beef--Chili (Box 22)
        - Bumble Bee tuna (Box 22)
        - Chicken, 1950s-1970s (Box 22)
        - Eckrich sausage (Box 22)
        - Franks and sausage, 1950s-1970s (Box 22)
        - Ham, 1950s-1970s (Box 22)
        - Hormel (Box 22)
        - Hygrade's (Box 22)
        - Oscar Mayer (Box 23)
        - Patrick Cudahy (Box 23)
        - Swift Premium meats and ice cream (Box 23)
        - Taylor ham (Box 23)
      - Miscellaneous products
        - Nuts, 1950s (Box 23)
        - Oils, 1950s-1960s (Box 23)
        - Pet food
          - Foster & Kleiser-produced advertisements, 1960s-1970s (Box 23)
          - Ken-l-Ration (Box 23)
        - Pop-Corn, 1950s-1960s (Box 23)
        - Various mixed products, 1940s-1960s (Box 23)
      - Prepared foods
        - Ashley's Mexican foods (Box 23)
        - Campbell's (Box 23)
        - Canned goods (Box 23)
        - Del Monte (Box 23)
        - Franco-American (Box 23)
        - Jell-O (General Foods) desserts (Box 23)
        - Knorr (Box 23)
        - Kraft (Box 23)
        - Libby's (Box 23)
        - Skippy peanut butter (Box 23)
        - Spaghetti, 1950s-1960s (Box 23)
        - Stokely-Van Camp (Box 23)
        - Van de Kamp's (Box 23)
      - Spreads and sauces
        - Ketchup
          - Brooks catsup and BBQ sauce (Box 23)
          - Heinz (Box 23)
          - Hunt's catsup (Box 23)
          - Miscellaneous, 1950s-1960s (Box 23)
        - Mayonnaise
          - Best Foods (Box 23)
          - Hellmann's (Box 23)
          - Miscellaneous, 1950s-1960s (Box 23)
        - Salt
          - Carey Brand (Box 23)
          - Morton (Box 23)
          - Sterling (Box 24)
        - Sugar
          - C and H (Box 24)
          - Holly (Box 24)
          - Jack Frost (Box 24)
          - Miscellaneous, 1960s (Box 24)
        - Syrup
          - Aunt Jemima: see Quaker Oats (Box 24)
          - Br'er Rabbit (Box 24)
          - Log Cabin (Box 24)
          - Miscellaneous, 1950s-1960s (Box 24)
        - Yeast ( Fleischmann's) (Box 24)
        - Miscellaneous sauces, 1950s-1960s (Box 24)
    - Household
      - Appliances
        - Air conditioning, 1960s (Box 24)
        - Chainsaws, 1950s-1960s
          - Homelite (Box 24)
          - Miscellaneous (Box 24)
        - Dishwashers
          - Hotpoint (Box 24)
          - Miscellaneous, 1960s (Box 24)
        - Freezers, 1950s-1960s (Box 24)
        - Ovens, 1960s (Box 24)
        - Refrigerators
          - General Electric (Box 24)
          - Miscellaneous (Box 24)
        - Stereos, 1960s (Box 24)
        - Telephones (Box 24)
        - Televisions
          - Admiral (Box 24)
          - Magnavox (Box 24)
          - Motorola (Box 24)
          - Philco (Box 24)
          - RCA Victor (Box 24)
          - Sony (Box 24)
          - Westinghouse (Box 24)
          - Zenith (Box 24)
        - Washers and dryers
          - General Electric (Box 24)
          - Norge (Box 24)
          - Philco (Box 24)
          - Speed Queen (Box 24)
          - Westinghouse (Box 24)
      - Cleaners and laundry supplies
        - Cleansers
          - Sapolio (Box 24)
          - Miscellaneous (Box 24)
        - Laundry, 1960s
          - Blue Cheer (Procter and Gamble) (Box 24)
          - White King detergent and bleach (Box 24)
          - Miscellaneous (Box 24)
      - Furnishings
        - Floor coverings--Rugs (Box 24)
        - Furniture/Bedding (Box 24)
        - Home equipment, 1960s (Box 24)
        - La-Z-Boy chairs (Box 24)
        - Mattresses and bedding
          - Sealy mattresses (Box 24)
          - Simmon's (Beauty Rest) mattresses (Box 24)
      - Heating and air conditioning (Box 25)
        - Air conditioning, 1960s (Box 25)
        - Bryant--Gas and air conditioning (Box 25)
        - Electric utilities (Box 25)
        - Gas--Home (Box 25)
        - Gas--Hot water, 1960s (Box 25)
        - Gas utilities, 1960s-1970s (Box 25)
        - Home heating, 1960s (Box 25)
      - Household goods
        - Paper products
          - Charmin bathroom tissue (Box 25)
          - Miscellaneous (Box 25)
        - Wax, 1940s-1950s (Box 25)
        - Wrap products, 1950s (Box 25)
        - Miscellaneous, 1950s-1960s (Box 25)
    - International (Australian posters) (Box 25)
    - Music (albums and tapes) (Box 25)
    - Personal products
      - Cannon towels and stockings (Box 25)
      - Duracell batteries (Box 25)
      - Watches
        - Seiko (Box 25)
        - Miscellaneous, 1960s (Box 25)
    - Political campaigns (Box 25)
    - Publications
      - Chicago Sunday Tribune (Box 25)
      - Globe-Democrat, 1950s-1960s (Box 25)
      - Life Magazine (Box 25)
      - Philadelphia Inquirer (Box 25)
      - Saturday Evening Post (Box 25)
      - Miscellaneous publications, 1950s-1960s (Box 25)
    - Public service
      - Easter Seals (Box 25)
      - Military recruiting
        - Air Force, Air National Guard (Box 25)
        - Army and Army Reserve (Box 25)
        - Marine Corps (Box 25)
        - Navy and Navy Reserve (Box 25)
      - Traffic safety, 1940s-1960s (Box 25)
      - U.S. Savings Bonds, 1960s (Box 25)
      - Miscellaneous public service, (2 folders) (Box 26)
    - Radio/Television (Box 26)
    - Real estate (Box 26)
    - Religions (Box 26)
    - Restaurants
      - Howard Johnson, 1950s (Box 26)
      - McDonald's (Box 26)
      - Miscellaneous, 1960s-1970s (Box 26)
    - Retail
      - Clothing
        - Clothing--Female (Box 26)
        - Clothing--Male (Box 26)
        - Curlee clothes (Box 26)
        - Dickies work clothes (Box 26)
        - Hart Schaffner and Marx (Box 26)
        - Jantzen (Box 26)
        - Kuppenheimer (Box 26)
        - Levi's (Box 26)
      - Department stores
        - Belk's (Box 26)
        - Bullock's (Box 26)
        - Hastings (Box 26)
        - J.W. Robinson Company (Los Angeles) (Box 26)
        - Macy's (Box 26)
        - Orbach's (Box 26)
        - Woolworth's (Box 26)
      - Drug stores (Box 26)
      - Florists (Box 26)
      - Footwear (Box 27)
        - Ked's (Box 27)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 27)
      - Grocery stores
        - Food and savings stamps (Box 27)
        - Safeway (Box 27)
        - Shoprite (Box 27)
        - Supermarkets, 1950s (Box 27)
        - Thorofare (Box 27)